bitok.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Secure Bitcoin exchange - Bitok.com

### PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Bitcoin Innovations Ltd (“Bitok.com”) stores, protects, and uses your personal information collected during your experience with our website www.bitok.com (“Site”) and Bitok.com service (“Service”). 

As used in the Privacy Policy, “Bitok.com”, “we”, “us” or “our” refers to the company Bitcoin Innovations Ltd, including, without limitations, its owners, directors, investors, employees and other related persons. Depending upon the context, “Bitok.com” may also refer to the services, products, website, content or other materials provided by Bitok.com. 

Capitalized terms not otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning as they defined in the Terms of Use . 

#### 1\. Collection and use of PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may collect your personal information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information about you when you register the Account, complete a transaction, fill out a form, respond to surveys, give us feedback or otherwise communicate with us.

The types of information we may collect, including but not limited to:

  * contact information, such as your name, home address, telephone number, and email address;
  * **identity verification information, such as images of your government issued ID, passport, national ID card, or driving license;**
  * residence verification information, such as utility bill details or similar information;
  * computer or mobile device information, including IP addresses;
  * account information, such as username and password.

In order to fulfil our legal obligations to prevent fraud, money laundering and terrorist financing, we may obtain personal information about you from third party agencies, including your financial history, county court judgements and bankruptcies, from credit reference and fraud prevention agencies when you open the Account and at any time when we feel it is necessary to prevent abovementioned activities and minimise our risks.

We may use your personal information, including, but not limited to:

  * process your transactions via the Service. We will process your personal information only for the purpose for which it has been provided to us;
  * verify your identity in accordance with the money laundering regulations and our KYC Policy;
  * improve our Service;
  * provide customer support;
  * administer a contest, promotion, survey or other features on the Site;
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * remain legally compliant.

#### 2\. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to third parties, law enforcement and government officials, and transfer your personal information outside the EEA, as described below.

##### 2.1 Disclosures to third parties

While processing your transactions, we may share some of your personal information with third party service providers who help with our business operations. Your information will not be sold, exchanged, or shared with any third parties without your consent, except to provide the Service or as required by law.

Non-personally identifiable user information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Our third party service providers are contractually bound to protect and use such information only for the purposes for which it was disclosed, except as otherwise required or permitted by law. We ensure that such third parties will be bound by terms no less protective those described in this Privacy Policy, or those we are subject to under applicable data protection laws.

##### 2.2. Disclosures to legal authorities

We may share your personal information with law enforcement, data protection authorities, government officials, and other authorities when:

  * compelled by subpoena, court order, or other legal procedure;
  * we believe that the disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss;
  * disclosure is necessary to report suspected illegal activity;
  * disclosure is necessary to investigate violations of this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use or any of our policies and regulations.

##### 2.3. International transfers of personal information

We store and process your personal information in data centres around the world, wherever Bitok.com facilities or service providers are located. As such, we may transfer your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). Such transfers are undertaken in accordance with our legal and regulatory obligations.

#### 3\. RETENTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We are required by law to retain certain records for a period of at least five (5) years after termination of your Account which may include your personal information such as your name, contact details, contact number, transaction history etc. Otherwise, we will delete and destroy all personal information that we hold about you when you (or we) terminate your Account. We do not store your online banking login PIN, TAN and password.

#### 4\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our Site contains links and references to other websites. You should be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites and we encourage you to read privacy policy of every website you visit.

#### 5\. COOKIES

We use a browser feature known as a “cookie”, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive. Information collected from cookies is used by us to evaluate the effectiveness of the Site and/or the Service. The information collected from cookies allows us to determine such things as which parts of our Site are most visited and difficulties our visitors may experience in accessing the Site and/or the Service. With this knowledge, we can improve the quality of your experience on the Site and/or the Service.

#### 6\. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of information we have physical, electronic and managerial procedures in place to keep your personal information safe. Once logged into your Account, all internet communication is secured using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security 128bit encryption.

However, this high level of protection can only be effective if you follow certain security practices yourself. You must never share your Account login details with anyone. If you are concerned that any of your login details have been compromised, you can change them any time once you are logged on but you should always also immediately contact us and tell us why you think your login details have been compromised. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Site. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your personal information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

BITOK.COM WILL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY LEAK OF PERSONAL INFORMATION CAUSED BY HACKING OR ANY OTHER CYBERCRIME.

#### 7\. AMENDMENTS AND MODIFICATIONS

This Privacy Policy may be revised, modified, or amended at any time, at the sole discretion of Bitok.com. You acknowledge and agree that it is your own responsibility to review the Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of amendments and modifications.

If you do not wish to accept the revised/modified/amended Privacy Policy, you should not continue to use the Service. Your continued use of the Site and/or the Service following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.

#### 8\. ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

If your personal information (such as your name, address, or telephone number) changes, you should update it. We shall not be liable for any loss arising out of your failure to keep your personal information up to date.

NOTE: You have the right to access information that we hold about you. To do so, please contact our [support](https://support.bitok.com/hc/en-us). Access may be subject to a fee.

#### 9\. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Site and/or the Service, you signify your acceptance of the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, please, do not use the Site and/or the Service. Your continued use of the Site and/or the Service following the posting of changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed as your acceptance of those changes.
